http://foxproject.org.uk/privacy-policy/

Donate now
Mobile ambulance: 01892 731565 (9am - 9pm)
Home / Privacy Policy
The following Privacy Statement explains how we The Fox Project collect, store and use your personal information.
Privacy Statement
We do not sell or share your data with any other company or charity.
We do not store credit and debit card details, these are destroyed immediately following any transaction and are never shared – even within the organisation – by email or other form of written communication. In this and other regards we are obliged to comply with annual security assessments stipulated by Worldpay.
How we use your information
We may process personal information in a number of ways, such as:
To process donations and Gift Aid
Process orders from our online shop
To provide any information you request from us
To keep you updated with our work and fundraising appeals (unless you ask us not to) via Social Media, mailings and emails
Newsletters and fund raising events
To carry out animal rescues and rehabilitation services through rescues, cage traps and fostering
Keeping you updated
We believe that it is important to keep our donors and supporters updated about how your generous support is making a difference to our vital work – unless you ask us not to.
When you provide your contact details to us we will normally ask which communication channels you prefer. You can change your preferences at any time by contacting us.
You have the opportunity to ‘unsubscribe’ at any time. Simply ring, post or email us requesting so.
Updating this statement
We may modify, alter or otherwise update this privacy policy at any time. You accept the most recent version of our Privacy Policy every time you enter and use this website. We encourage you to review this policy from time to time.
Help make a difference
We do not receive financial support from national or local government. We rely entirely on donations from our supporters.
Donate now
Mobile Ambulance (9am-9pm Daily)
01892 731565
Broadwater Forest Wildlife Hospital,
Fairview Lane,
Tunbridge Wells,
Kent,
Whats Going on in the media?
